Alright, let's keep it going. What do we need to do next,
好的，让我们继续，下一步我们该做些什么？
we're gonna go ahead and eat our withdrawal function here.
我们要继续编写我们的提款函数
So let's create that
我们来创建一下它
this is gonna look really similar to everything we've done so far.
就和我们之前做的工作很相似
So on our index dot HTML, let's create a new button
所以我们要在 "index.html" 里，创建一个新的按钮
that we can do by copying this whole line, paste it underneath,
我们可以复制这一整行，粘贴到下面
call this withdraw button, we'll call withdraw. And we'll call this withdraw.
命名为 "withdraw"，这里是 "withdraw"，这里是 "withdrawButton"
And then in our index, do the same thing,
然后在 "index" 里，还是做一样的事
we'll copy this, paste it below.
复制这个，粘贴到下面
So with drop button was document get element by ID, withdraw button,
改成 `withdrawButton = document.getElementById("withdrawButton")`
withdraw button.on Click equals withdraw.
`withdrawButton.onclick = withdraw`
So let's make a withdrawal function down at the bottom.
让我们在底部创建一个 "withdraw" 函数
We'll go ahead, say async. Function withdraw,
继续写 `async function withdraw()`
will do the exact same that we've done above.
接下来就和我们上面做的事完全一样
And I can even just copy everything from the get balance and just remove the balance section.
我甚至可以复制 "getBalance" 的所有内容，然后删掉关于 "balance" 部分
If type of window dot Aetherium does not equal to undefined,
`if (typeof window.ethereum != "undefined")`
then we'll grab the provider here.
接着获取这里的 "provider"
And same as the fund contract, we'll grab the signer and the contract.
然后就和 "fund" 合约一样，我们要获取 "signer" 以及 "contract"
(译者注：这里指的应该是 "fund" 函数)
So let's just grab those two lines. Paste them down here
所以让我们获取这两行，粘贴到这里
called signer equals provider dot get signer.
`const signer = provider.getSigner()`
Contract equals new contract, blah, blah, blah. Okay, cool.
`contract = new Contract` blah, blah, blah，OK 酷，
Now we're gonna do the exact same here as we did with the fun function.
现在我们要进行的是和 "fund" 函数中完全一样的操作
So we're gonna do a little try, catch, and then we'll even add the catch here, catch error, console dot log error.
也就是 `try-catch`，我们在这里添加一个 `catch(error)`
And inside of our try, we'll do const transaction response equals await, contracts dot withdraw.
在 "try" 的内部，我们要写 `const transactionResponse = await contract.withdraw()`
We don't need to put any parameters in here.
我们不需要在这里放入任何参数
Oh, then actually, let's do a little console dot log, withdrawing,
哦，其实这里还有一句 `console.log("Withdrawing...")`
and then we'll get this transaction response.
然后我们就会获得这个 "transactionResponse"
And then we'll listen for this transaction to get mined as well.
接着我们就要监听这笔交易是否被挖掘了出来
By running a Wait, listen for transaction mine transaction response comma, provider
运行 `await listenForTransactionMine(transactionResponse, provider)`
And that's it, since we can reuse the functionality from our listen for transaction mine.
这就结束了，因为我们可以复用 "listenForTransactionMine" 这个函数
So now we'll refresh, we'll make sure we're connected,
现在我们刷新一下，确保我们已经连接上了
check the current balance, which is 3.8.
查看余额，是 3.8
Now we'll go ahead and withdraw.
现在我们点击 "withdraw"
We see our little withdrawing console dot log, we'll hit Confirm.
可以看到 "console.log" 输出的 "withdrawing"，点击“确认”("Confirm")
And it looks like we've completed it,
看起来我们已经完成了
if we look in our Metamask, our bounced will have been increased by the amount that was added here.
如果查看一下我们的 MetaMask，我们的账户余额将会增加刚刚添加的金额
And now if we hit balance, we do indeed see zero,
现在如果我们点击一下余额，确实是变成 0 了
we can even double check that this is actually working,
我们甚至可以再次确认一下这是否是真的生效了
we can see our balance is 9.99. Let's go ahead and even fund this with 99 eath.
可以看到我们的余额是 9.99，我们注入 99 以太币的资金
Good confirm, looks like it's completed.
点击“确认”("Confirm")，看起来已经完成了
Our meta mask now shows 99.00.
现在我们的 MetaMask 显示 99.00
And if we go ahead and withdraw, confirm, that withdrawal has gone through,
我们继续，点击 "withdraw"，“确认”("Confirm")，提款已经通过
we can see our balance is back up to 9999.
我们可以看到，余额已经回到了 9999！